<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedDate="2024-10-25T23:53:46">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>All Creatures Of Our God And King</title>
    </titles>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <authors>
      <author>St. Francis of Assisi William Henry Draper</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>All creatures of our God and King, newline Lift up your voice and with us sing, newline Alleluia! Alleluia! newline Thou burning sun with golden beam, newline Thou silver moon with softer gleam, newline O praise Him, O praise Him! newline Alleluia! Alleluia! Alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Thou rushing wind that art so strong, newline Ye clouds that sail in heaven along, newline O praise Him! Alleluia! newline Thou rising morn, in praise rejoice; newline Ye lights of evening, find a voice! newline O praise Him, O praise Him! newline Alleluia! Alleluia! Alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Thou flowing water, pure and clear, newline Make music for thy Lord to hear. newline Alleluia! Alleluia! newline Thou fire so masterful and bright, newline Thou givest man both warmth and light! newline O praise Him, O praise Him! newline Alleluia! Alleluia! Alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>And all ye men of tender heart, newline Forgiving others take your part. newline O sing ye! Alleluia! newline Ye who long pain and sorrow bear, newline Praise God and on Him cast your care! newline O praise Him, O praise Him! newline Alleluia! Alleluia! Alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Let all things their Creator bless, newline And worship Him in humbleness. newline O praise Him! Alleluia! newline Praise, praise the Father, praise the Son, newline And praise the Spirit, Three in One! newline O praise Him! O praise Him! newline Alleluia! Alleluia! Alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Earth ever fertile day by day, newline Bring forth Your blessings on our way, newline O praise Him! Alleluia! newline All fruit and crops that richly grow, newline All trees and flowers God's glory show. newline O praise Him! O praise Him! newline Alleluia! Alleluia! Alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>People and nations take your part, newline Love and forgive with all your heart, newline Alleluia! Alleluia! newline All who long pain and sorrow bear, newline Trust God and cast on Him your care. newline O praise Him! O praise Him! newline Alleluia! Alleluia! Alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v8">
      <lines>Death once the ancient enemy, newline Hear now our Easter melody, newline O praise Him! Alleluia! newline You are the pathway home to God, newline Our door to life through Christ our Lord. newline O praise Him! O praise Him! newline Alleluia! Alleluia! Alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v9">
      <lines>Praise God from whom all blessings flow; newline Praise Him all creatures here below; newline O praise Him! Alleluia! newline Praise Him above ye heavenly hosts, newline Praise Father, Son, and Holy Ghost. newline O praise Him, O praise Him! newline Alleluia! Alleluia! Alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v10">
      <lines>Dear mother earth, who day by day newline Unfoldest blessings on our way, newline O praise Him! Alleluia! newline The flowers and fruits that in Thee grow, newline Let them His glory also show; newline O praise Him, O praise Him! newline Alleluia! Alleluia! Alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v11">
      <lines>And thou, most kind and gentle death, newline Waiting to hush our latest breath, newline O praise Him, Alleluia! newline Thou leadest home the child of God, newline And Christ our Lord the way hath trod; newline O praise Him, O praise Him! newline Alleluia! Alleluia! Alleluia!</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
