<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedDate="2024-10-25T23:53:46">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>And Can It Be</title>
    </titles>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <authors>
      <author>Charles Wesley Thomas Campbell</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>Amazing love! How can it be newline That Thou, my God, shouldst die for me?</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>And can it be that I should gain newline An interest in the Savior's blood? newline Died He for me, who caused His pain? newline For me, who Him to death pursued?</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>He left His Father's throne above, newline So free, so infinite His grace; newline Emptied Himself of all but love, newline And bled for Adam's helpless race. newline 'Tis mercy all, immense and free! newline For, O my God it found out me!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>No condemnation now I dread; newline Jesus, and all in Him, is mine! newline Alive in Him my living Head, newline And clothed in righteousness divine, newline Bold I approach the eternal throne, newline And claim the crown, through Christ my own.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>'Tis mystery all! The Immortal dies! newline Who can explore His strange design? newline In vain the first born seraph tries newline To sound the depths of love divine! newline 'Tis mercy all! Let earth adore, newline Let angel minds inquire no more.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Long my imprisoned Spirit lay newline Fast bound in sin and nature's night; newline Thine eye diffused a quickening ray, newline I woke, the dungeon flamed with light; newline My chains fell off, my heart was free; newline I rose, went forth and followed Thee.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
