<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedDate="2024-10-25T23:53:47">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Crown Him With Many Crowns</title>
    </titles>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <authors>
      <author>George J. Elvey Godfrey Thring Matthew Bridges</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Crown Him with many crowns, newline The Lamb upon His throne. newline Hark! how the heavenly anthem drowns newline All music but its own! newline Awake, my soul and sing newline Of Him who died for Thee; newline And hail Him as thy matchless King newline Through all eternity.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Crown Him the Lord of love: newline Behold His hands and side, newline Rich wounds, yet visible above, newline In beauty glorified; newline No angel in the sky newline Can fully bear that sight, newline But downwards bends His wondering eye newline At mysteries so bright.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Crown Him the Lord of life, newline Who triumphed o'er the grave. newline Who rose victorious to the strife, newline For those He came to save. newline His glories now we sing, newline Who died and rose on high. newline Who died eternal life to bring, newline And lives that death may die.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Crown Him the Lord of peace, newline Whose pow'r a scepter sways newline From pole to pole, newline That wars may cease newline And all be prayer and praise; newline His reign shall know no end, newline And round His pierced feet newline Fair flowers of paradise extend newline Their fragrance ever sweet.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Crown Him the Lord of years, newline The Potentate of time; newline Creator of the rolling spheres, newline Ineffably sublime. newline All hail, Redeemer, hail! newline For Thou hast died for me. newline Thy praise and glory shall not fail newline Throughout eternity.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Crown Him the Son of God newline Before the worlds began, newline And ye, who tread where He hath trod, newline Crown Him the Son of man; newline Who every grief hath known newline That wrings the human breast, newline And takes and bears them for His own, newline That all in Him may rest.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>Crown Him the Lord of heaven: newline One with the Father known, newline One with the Spirit newline Through Him given newline From yonder glorious throne. newline All hail, Redeemer, hail! newline For Thou hast died for me; newline Thy praise and glory shall not fail newline Throughout eternity.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
