<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedDate="2024-10-25T23:53:48">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>It Came Upon A Midnight Clear</title>
    </titles>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <authors>
      <author>Edmund H. Sears Richard S. Willis</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>It came upon the midnight clear, newline That glorious song of old; newline From angels bending near the earth newline To touch their harps of gold. newline "Peace on the earth good will to men, newline From heaven's all gracious King!" newline The world in solemn stillness lay newline To hear the angels sing.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Still thro' the cloven skies they come, newline With peaceful wings unfurled; newline And still their heavenly music floats, newline O'er all the weary world. newline Above its sad and lowly plains, newline They bend on hovering wing; newline And ever o'er its Babel sounds newline The blessed angels sing.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>And ye, beneath life's crushing load, newline Whose forms are bending low; newline Who toil along the climbing way newline With painful steps and slow. newline Look now! for glad and golden hours, newline Come swiftly on the wing; newline O rest beside the weary road, newline And hear the angels sing.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>For lo, the days are hastening on, newline By prophet bards foretold; newline When with the ever circling years, newline Comes round the age of gold. newline When peace shall over all the earth, newline Its ancient splendors fling; newline And the whole world give back the song newline Which now the angels sing.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Yet with the woes of sin and strife newline The world has suffered long; newline Beneath the angel strain have rolled, newline Two thousand years of wrong. newline And man, at war with man, hears not, newline The love song which they bring; newline O hush the noise, ye men of strife, newline And hear the angels sing.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
