<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedDate="2024-10-25T23:53:48">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>O Come O Come Emmanuel</title>
    </titles>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <authors>
      <author>Henry S. Coffin John M. Neale Thomas Helmore</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="c1">
      <lines>Rejoice! Rejoice! Emmanuel, newline Shall come to thee, O Israel!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>O come, O come Emmanuel newline And ransom captive Israel, newline That mourns in lonely exile here newline Until the Son of God appear.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>O come, thou Wisdom from on high, newline And order all things far and nigh; newline To us the path of knowledge show newline And cause us in her ways to go.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>O come, O come, great Lord of might, newline Who to Thy tribes on Sinai's height newline In ancient times once gave the law newline In cloud and majesty and awe.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>O come, thou Root of Jesse's tree, newline An ensign of Thy people be; newline Before Thee rulers silent fall; newline All peoples on Thy mercy call.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>O come, thou Key of David, come, newline And open wide our heavenly home. newline The captives from their prison free, newline And conquer death's deep misery.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>O come, thou Dayspring, come and cheer newline Our spirits by Thy justice here; newline Disperse the gloomy clouds of night, newline And death's dark shadows put to flight.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>O come, Desire of nations bind newline All peoples in one heart and mind. newline From dust Thou brought us forth to life; newline Deliver us from earthly strife.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
