<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedDate="2024-10-25T23:53:48">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Star Spangled Banner</title>
    </titles>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <authors>
      <author>Francis Scott Key John Stafford Smith</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Oh, say, can you see, newline By the dawn's early light, newline What so proudly we hailed newline At the twilight's last gleaming? newline Whose broad stripes and bright stars, newline Thro' the perilous fight, newline O'er the ramparts we watched, newline Were so gallantly streaming? newline And the rocket's red glare, newline The bombs bursting in air, newline Gave proof thro' the night, newline That our flag was still there. newline Oh, say, does that star-spangled newline Banner yet wave newline O'er the land of the free, newline And the home of the brave?</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Oh, thus be it ever, newline When freemen shall stand newline Between their loved homes, newline And the war's desolation; newline Blest with vict'ry and peace, newline May the heav'n rescued land newline Praise the Pow'r that hath made. newline And preserved us a nation! newline Then conquer we must, newline When our cause it is just; newline And this be our motto: newline "In God is our trust!" newline And the star-spangled banner newline In triumph shall wave newline O'er the land of the free, newline And the home of the brave.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>On the shore, dimly seen newline Thro' the mists of the deep, newline Where the foe's haughty host newline In dread silence reposes, newline What is that which the breeze, newline O'er the towering steep, newline As it fitfully blows, newline Half conceals, half discloses? newline Now it catches the gleam newline Of the morning's first beam, newline In full glory reflected, newline Now shines on the stream: newline 'Tis the star-spangled banner; newline Oh, long may it wave newline O'er the land of the free, newline And the home of the brave.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>And where is that band, newline Who so vauntingly swore newline That the havoc of war newline And the battle's confusion, newline A home and a country newline Should leave us no more? newline Their blood has washed out newline Their foul footsteps' pollution; newline No refuge could save newline The hireling and slave newline From the terror of flight newline Or the gloom of the grave. newline And the star-spangled banner newline In triumph shall wave newline O'er the land of the free, newline And the home of the brave.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
