<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedDate="2024-10-25T23:53:48">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>Sweet Hour Of Prayer</title>
    </titles>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <authors>
      <author>William B. Bradbury William W. Walford</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>Sweet hour of prayer, newline Sweet hour of prayer, newline That calls me from a world of care newline And bids me at my Father's throne newline Make all my wants and wishes known. newline In seasons of distress and grief newline My soul has often found relief, newline And oft escaped the tempter's snare, newline By Thy return sweet hour of prayer.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Sweet hour of prayer, newline Sweet hour of prayer. newline The joys I feel, the bliss I share. newline Of those whose anxious spirits burn newline With strong desires for Thy return. newline With such I hasten to the place newline Where God, my Savior, shows His face. newline And gladly take my station there, newline And wait for Thee, sweet hour of prayer.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Sweet hour of prayer, newline Sweet hour of prayer, newline Thy wings shall my petition bear newline To Him whose truth and faithfulness newline Engage the waiting soul to bless; newline And since He bids me seek His face, newline Believe His word, and trust His grace, newline I'll cast on Him my ev'ry care. newline And wait for Thee, sweet hour of prayer.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Sweet hour of prayer, newline Sweet hour of prayer, newline May I Thy consolation share, newline 'Til from Mount Pisgah's lofty height, newline I view my home and take my flight. newline This robe of flesh newline I'll drop and rise newline To seize the everlasting prize, newline And shout while passing through the air, newline Farewell, farewell sweet hour of prayer.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
