<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedDate="2024-10-25T23:53:49">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>There Is A Fountain</title>
    </titles>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <authors>
      <author>Lowell Mason William Cowper</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>There is a fountain filled with blood newline Drawn from Immanuel's veins; newline And sinners, plunged beneath that flood, newline Lose all their guilty stains: newline Lose all their guilty stains, newline Lose all their guilty stains; newline And sinners, plunged beneath that flood, newline Lose all their guilty stains.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>The dying thief rejoiced to see newline That fountain in his day; newline And there may I, though vile as he, newline Wash all my sins away: newline Wash all my sins away, newline Wash all my sins away; newline And there may I, though vile as he, newline Wash all my sins away.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>Dear dying Lamb, Thy precious blood newline Shall never lose its power newline Till all the ransomed church of God newline Are saved, to sin no more: newline Are saved, to sin no more, newline Are saved, to sin no more; newline Till all the ransomed church of God newline Are saved, to sin no more.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>For since by faith I saw the stream newline Thy flowing wounds supply, newline Redeeming love has been my theme, newline And shall be till I die: newline And shall be till I die, newline And shall be till I die; newline Redeeming love has been my theme newline And shall be till I die.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>When this poor lisping, stamm'ring tongue newline Lies silent in the grave, newline Then in a nobler, sweeter song newline I'll sing Thy pow'r to save: newline Then in a nobler sweeter song newline I'll sing Thy pow'r to save; newline I'll sing Thy pow'r to save, newline I'll sing Thy pow'r to save; newline Then in a nobler sweeter song newline I'll sing Thy pow'r to save.</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>E'er since by faith I saw the stream newline Thy flowing wounds supply, newline Redeeming love has been my theme, newline And shall be till I die: newline And shall be till I die, newline And shall be till I die; newline Redeeming love has been my theme, newline And shall be till I die.</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
