<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<song xmlns="http://openlyrics.info/namespace/2009/song" version="0.8" createdIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedIn="OpenLP 3.1.3" modifiedDate="2024-10-25T23:53:49">
  <properties>
    <titles>
      <title>When Morning Gilds The Skies</title>
    </titles>
    <copyright>Public Domain</copyright>
    <authors>
      <author>Edward Caswall Joseph Barnby</author>
    </authors>
  </properties>
  <lyrics>
    <verse name="v1">
      <lines>When morning gilds the skies, newline My heart awaking cries; newline May Jesus Christ be praised! newline Alike at work and prayer, newline To Jesus I repair; newline May Jesus Christ be praised!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v2">
      <lines>Does sadness fill my mind? newline A solace here I find; newline May Jesus Christ be praised! newline Or fades my earthly bliss? newline My comfort still is this; newline May Jesus Christ be praised!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v3">
      <lines>The night becomes as day, newline When from the heart we say, newline May Jesus Christ be praised! newline The pow'rs of darkness fear newline When this sweet chant they hear; newline May Jesus Christ be praised!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v4">
      <lines>Ye nations of mankind, newline In this your concord find; newline May Jesus Christ be praised! newline Let all the earth around newline Ring joyous with the sound; newline May Jesus Christ be praised!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v5">
      <lines>Sing, suns and stars of space, newline Sing, ye that see His face; newline May Jesus Christ be praised! newline God's whole creation o'er, newline For aye and evermore; newline May Jesus Christ be praised!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v6">
      <lines>Be this, while life is mine, newline My canticle divine; newline May Jesus Christ be praised! newline Be this the eternal song newline Thro' all the ages long; newline May Jesus Christ be praised!</lines>
    </verse>
    <verse name="v7">
      <lines>Whene'er the sweet church bell newline Peals over hill and dell newline May Jesus Christ be praised! newline O hark to what it sings, newline As joyously it rings, newline May Jesus Christ be praised!</lines>
    </verse>
  </lyrics>
</song>
